Pola Gur

Israel +972584105011 pola.gur.il@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2020, Saint Petersburg State Institute of Psychology and Social Work, BA in Psychology.

2012, graduated Engineering Lyceum NSTU, Novosibirsk State Technical University

ADVANCED EDUCATION AND TRAINING

- 2021 mini course "integrative psychotherapy of neuroses and panic attacks"
- 2021 online conference "Aggressive behavior of children. Modern psychologist tools for working with parents and children"
- 2019 Refresher course "Psychotherapy of intimate and sexual relations"
- 2018 2019 Psychological Therapy Workshop (Saint Petersburg)
- Since 2018 Guest lecturer (lectures and trainings in psychology, conflictology, pedagogy and andragogy)
- Since 2018 Private practice (counseling)
- 2018 Seminar "Information potential of biological objects"
- 2017 2018 Madrichim school JAFI (Saint Petersburg)
- 2017 Training of tutors for special children (2 levels)
- 2015, 2016 Conference media magazine "Psychotherapy in Russia" (Saint Petersburg)
- 2015 2016 Capacity Building (St. Petersburg – Cleveland). Program for leaders and executive of Jewish organizations
- 2015 Training Madrichim for Taglit Birthright Israel (Israel)
- 2014 Madrichim school GPG (Saint Petersburg)
- 2014 Madrichim school Adain Lo (Saint Petersburg)
- 2009 2013 camp counselors' seminars on teaching methods

LANGUAGES

- Russian (native)
- English (intermediate)
- Hebrew (Intermediate)
- · German (begginer, in progress)

SUMMARY

Educator and andragogue with fourteen years of experience, Bachelor of Psychology and volunteer in inclusive social and environmental projects. Quick learner, confident use of digital tools, with experience in creating and managing projects and expeditions from scratch to implementation.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Since 2023 — Madricha in Giv'olim School

Since 2022 — Educator in Kehilat Daniel in Jaffa — Reform Jewish community in Jaffa

2022 — 2023 — children's program manager in Jewish Point (children's program manager (full cycle: communication with parents, recruitment of presenters, scheduling, purchasing, keeping children's personal files), later kindergarten director 2022 — 2023 — madricha in special education (school "Oz") 2020 — 2021 — Jewish educator in kindergarten Tapuz (JCC

Moscow)
Since 2020 — Teacher in PJ Library

2020 — online summer camps and programs (J-camp, JAFI, Netzer, PJ Library)

Since 2019 — Head of Madrichim School (Hillel Moscow). Developed and conducted a leadership program for students, attracting external specialists (lectures, trainings, practical exercises)

2019 — 2020 — Trainer, methodologist, tutorial developer in Presium Education. Taught structural thinking and visualization skills of managers and middle management (Ministry of Finance, banks, advertising and fuel companies).

Since 2018 — Madricha and Rosh Tzevet JAFI camps 2017 — 2019 — ambassador of the Global Day of Jewish learning in FSU

2015 — 2018 — coordinator of the project "Jewish Studies for teenagers from across FSU" in the Resource Center of jewish education. Keeps a tight connection with more than 20 regions FSU and different community (JCC, Hillel, Israel cultural center and teen club "tzameret", JAFI, local organizations like Sunday schools, camps, synagogues)

As a result of the work of Madricha Taglit (since 2015), there are links with representatives of JAFI in Israel and specialists (guides, historians, archaeologists)

2013 — 2018 — work in family Jewish center "Adain Io" (camps, kindergarten, inclusive social program)

2007 - 2014 — organizational work in youth clubs, camps, center of animation pedagogy

INTERESTS

- Cognitive sciences, neuroscience, brain function, developmental disorders, psychology, interpersonal relationships,
- Languages